Privacy Policy

Last update: 17/07/2023 Version: 3.0

This privacy policy governs the processing of personal data collected through the website

https://www.throwawaymail.com/, the related mobile applications and services (collectively,

“Website”). Please read this document carefully to make sure that you understand how we handle

your personal data. If you have any further questions regarding our data protection

practices, please feel free to contact us.

Our privacy policy explains in detail:

• What personal data (“PD”) and non-personal data (“NPD”) we collect from you, for what

purposes we use it, how we protect it, and how we share it with third parties;

• How you can access and change your PD and how you can limit our sharing of it; and

• Your legal rights that you have with respect to your PD.

The topics covered in this privacy policy include:

1\. General Information and Definitions 1

2\. Types and Purposes of PD and NPD that We Process 2

3\. Sharing Your PD and NPD with Third Parties 4

4\. Transfer of PD Outside Your Country 6

5\. Retaining and Destroying Your PD and NPD 7

6\. Your Rights Regarding Your PD 7

7\. Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties 9

8\. Do Not Track Settings 9

9\. Links to Third-Party Websites 9

10\. Protecting Children’s Privacy 9

11\. Our Email Policy 9

12\. Our Security Policy 10

13\. Personalised (Targeted) Advertising 10

14\. Term and Changes to Our Privacy Policy 11

15\. Contact Us 12

1\. General Information and Definitions

1.1 About the Website. The Website allows you to generate a throwaway email.

1.2 Our role as a data controller. The entity that is responsible for the processing of your

PD though the Website is Landocs Ventures LTD having an address at Hasaham 30, Petah

tiqwa, 49517 Is rael (“we”, “us”, and “our”). We act as a data controller with regard

to your PD collected through the Website (e .g., when you register your user account, browse the

Website, or communicate with us) because we make decisions about the types of PD that should

be collected from you and the purposes for which such PD should be used.

1.3 Applicable laws. We process PD in accordance with applicable data protection laws,

including, but not limited to, the Israeli Protection of Privacy Law, the EU General Data Protection

Regulation (“GDPR”), and the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”).

1.4 Definitions. In this privacy policy, you will encounter recurrent terms . For your

convenience, we would like to explain what they mean:

• “NPD” means non-personal data that does not allow us to identify you in any manner;

• “PD” means personal data, i.e., any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural

person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by

reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online

identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental,

economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. PD is in many ways the same as

Personally Identifiable Information (PII). However, PD is broader in scope and covers more

data.

• “Visitor” is someone who merely browses our Website. A “member” is someone who

has registered with us to use our services. The terms “ user”, “you”, and “your” are collective

identifiers that refer to either a visitor or a member.

• “Consent” means a freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous agreement to the

processing of PD.

• “Data controller” means the entity that determines the purposes and means of the

processing of PD.

• “Data processor” means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body

which processes personal data on behalf of the data controller.

• “Processing” means the use of PD in any manner, including, but not limited to,

collection, storage, erasure, transfer, and disclosure of personal data.

1.5 Cookies. We use cookies on the Website. For more information on the types and

purposes of our cookies, please refer to our cookie policy available at

https://www.throwawaymail.com/cookie-policy.pdf.

2\. Types and Purposes of PD and NPD that We Process

2.1 PD that we collect. We comply with data minimisation principles and collect only a

minimal amount of PD that is necessary to ensure your proper use of the Website. The types of

PD that we collect and process are listed below. We process your PD only for specified and

legitimate purposes explicitly mentioned in this privacy policy. In short, we will use your PD only

for the purposes of enabling you to use the full functionality of the Website, providing you with the

requested services, maintaining and improving the Website, conducting research about our

business activities, administrative purposes, and replying to your enquiries. The detailed

description of the purposes and legal basis for processing of your PD is provided below.

Situation/PD Purpose Legal basis

When you register your user

account, we collect your:

• Email address

• Username

• Password

• Picture

When you register your user

account by using your Facebook

account, we collect your:

• Email address

• Full name

• Picture

• Other information that you

allow Facebook to share

• To create and maintain your user

account

• To provide access to the Website

• To provide you with the requested

services

• To contact you, if necessary

• To ensure security of the Website

• Performing a contract

with you

• Pursuing our legitimate

business interests (i.e.,

to ensure security)

• Your consent (optional

personal data)

When you contact us by email or

through the contact form, we

collect your:

• Name

• Email address

• Information you provide in

your message

▪ To respond to your enquiries

▪ To provide you with the requested

information

• Pursuing our legitimate

business interests (i.e., to

grow and promote our

business)

• Your consent (for

optional personal data)

When you use the Website, we

collect your:

• IP address

• Cookie-related data

(please refer to our cookie

policy for more information)

• To analyse, improve, and evaluate

our business activities

• To personalise the Website for your

location

• To ensure security of the Website

• Pursuing our legitimate

business interests (i.e.,

to analyse and improve

our business activities

and ensure security)

• Your consent (for certain

cookie-related data)

When you are served advertisement

on the Website, the following PD

and NPD is collected from you:\*

• IP address;

• Geographic location;

• Advertising ID;

• Your access and use patterns;

and

• Information about redirection to

other websites related to the

advertisement.

\*Please refer to section 13 for

more information.

• To tailor the advertisement to you;

• To retarget content to you;

• To personalise your experience on the

Website.

• Your consent; or

• Pursuing our legitimate

business interests (i.e.,

to support and expand

our business).

2.2 NPD that we collect. When you use the Website, we automatically receive information

from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from

which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website you’ll visit when you

leave our Website. This information also includes your Internet service provider’s name, your

web browser type, the type of mobile device, your computer operating system, and data about

your browsing activity when using our Website. We use all this NPD to (i) analyse trends among

our users to help improve our Website, (ii) identify and fix errors, and (iii) develop additional

features and services.

2.3 PD obtained from third parties. When using the Website, you can choose to permit

or restrict services, functionalities, and integrations provided by third parties, including, but not

limited to, social media service providers (“Third-Party Services”). Once enabled, the

providers of the Third-Party Services may share certain information and PD with us, subject to

the privacy policy of the Third-Party Services. We will use such PD only for the purposes for which

it was provided. You are strongly encouraged to check carefully the privacy settings and notices of

the Third-Party Services to understand what information may be disclosed to us.

2.4 What Happens If You Don’t Give Us Your PD? If you do not provide us with the PD

when requested, we may not be able to provide you with all our products and services. However,

you can access and use some parts of our Website without giving us your PD.

2.5 Sensitive data. We do not intentionally collect special categories of personal data

(‘sensitive data’), such as opinions about your religious and political beliefs, racial origins,

membership of a professional or trade association, or information about sexual orientation.

2.6 Your feedback. If you contact us, we may keep records of any questions, complaints

or compliments made by you and the response, if any. Where possible, we will de-identify your PD.

Please note that de-identified PD is also considered to be NPD.

2.7 Aggregated data. In case your NPD is combined with certain elements of your PD in a

way that allows us to identify you, we will handle such aggregated data as PD. If your PD is

de-identified in a way that it can no longer be associated with an identified or identifiable natural

person, it will not be considered PD and we may use it for any legitimate business purpose.

3\. Sharing Your PD and NPD with Third Parties

3.1 Selling your PD and NPD. WE DO NOT SELL YOUR PD TO THIRD PARTIES FOR

MARKETING OR OTHER PURPOSES. The term “sell” refers to selling, renting, releasing,

disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in

writing, or by electronic or other means, your PD by us to another business or a third party for

monetary or other valuable consideration. For data aggregation purposes, we may use your

NPD, which might be sold to other parties at our discretion. Any such data aggregation would

not contain any of your PD.

3.2 Sharing PD with our data processors. If necessary for the purposes listed below, we

will share your PD specified in section 2.1 with our third-party service providers we hire to provide

services to us (“Our Processors”). Our Processors include, but are not limited to, web analytics

companies, advertising networks, call centres, data management services, help desk providers,

accountants, law firms, auditors, shopping cart and email service

providers. The disclosure of your PD to Our Processors is limited to the situations when such data

is required for the following purposes:

● Ensuring the proper operation of our Website;

● Ensuring the delivery of the services requested by you;

● Providing you with the requested information;

● Pursuing our legitimate business interests;

● Enforcing our rights, preventing fraud, and security purposes;

● Carrying out our contractual obligations;

● Law enforcement purposes; or

● If you provide your prior consent to such a disclosure.

3.3 List of Our Processors. We will share your personal data only with Our Processors that

ag ree to ensure an adequate level of protection of personal data that is consistent with this

privacy policy and the applicable data protection laws. Our Processors that may have access to

your PD are listed below.

Service Name Location More information

Hosting service

provider

Linode \& Amazon

(AWS)

Linode hosting –

Texas, US

AWS – Virginia

US

https://www.linode.com/

https://aws.amazon.com/

Business analytics

service provider Google Analytics United States https://analytics.google.com

Header bidding

partner Adapex United States https://adapex.io/

Email service provider Sendgrid United States https://sendgrid.com

Technical support

service providers

IT Syndicate IT Syndicate HongKong

Freshdesk United States https://freshdesk.com

Automated Video

advertising partner Primis Israel https://www.primis.tech/

Advertising network Google Adexchange United States https://admanager.google.com/ho

me/

Our group of

companies Landocs Holdings Ltd, Ran Ventures Ltd, Komantra Holdings Ltd, Keeper Holdings Ltd

Software developing

partners and business

advisors

Independent contractors

3.4 Legally required releases of PD. We may be legally required to disclose your PD if

such disclosure is: (i) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (ii) necessary to assist law

enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (iii) necessary to

investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our legal terms ; (iv) necessary to protect us from

legal action or claims from third parties, including you and/or other users or members; or (v)

necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property , or personal safety of our company,

users, employees, and affiliates.

3.5 Disclosures to successors. If our business is sold or merges in whole or in part with

another business that would become responsible for providing the Website to you, we retain the

right to transfer your PD to the new business. The new business would retain the right to use your

PD according to the terms of this privacy policy as well as to any changes to this privacy policy

as instituted by the new business. We also retain the right to transfer your PD if our company files

for bankruptcy and some or all of our assets are sold to another individual or business.

3.6 Disclosure of NPD. We may disclose your NPD and de-identified PD for any purpose.

For example, we may share it with prospects or partners for business or research purposes, for

improving the Website, responding to lawful requests from public authorities, or developing new

products and services.

3.7 Google reCAPCHA. We have implemented reCAPCHA, the service provided by

Google (Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) to verify

whether you are a human being and not a robot. It helps to protect the Website against spam and

abuse. When you use reCAPCHA, Google will collect some PD and NPD from you, such as (i)

cookie-related data, (ii) your IP address, (iii) information about your mouse clicks, (iv) CSS

information of the Website, (v ) date, (vi) browser language,

(vii) plug-ins installed in the browser, and (viii) javascript objects. Such data will be sent to Google.

We have a legitimate interest in protecting the Website from abusive automated crawling and

spam. For more information about Google reCAPTCHA and Google's privacy policy, please visit

the following links: https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/ and

https://www.google.com/recaptcha/intro/android.html.

4\. Transfer of PD Outside Your Country

4.1 The PD that we collect from you may be stored , processed, and transferred between any

of the countries in which we or Our Processors operate. For example, if you reside in the

European Economic Area (EEA), we may need to transfer your personal data to jurisdictions

outside the EEA.

4.2 Wherever we transfer, process or store your PD, we will take reasonable steps to protect

it. For example, we will make sure that the jurisdiction in which the recipient third party is located

guarantees an adequate level of protection for your PD (e .g., the country in which the recipient

is located is white-listed by the European Commission or the recipient is a Privacy-Shield

certified entity) or we conclude an agreement with the respective third party that ensures such

protection (e.g., a data processing agreement based on the Standard Contractual Clauses

provided by the European Commission).

4.3 The European Commission has not found the United States and some other countries

where we and our Processors are located to have an adequate level of protection of PD under

Article 45 of the GDPR. We rely on derogations for specific situations as defined in Article 49 of the

GDPR. We will use your PD to provide the goods, services, and/or

information you request from us to perform a contract with you or to satisfy a legitimate interest of

our company in a manner that does not outweigh your freedoms and rights.

5\. Retaining and Destroying Your PD and NPD

5.1 Retention of PD. We retain information that we collect from you (including your PD) only

for as long as we need it for legal, business, or tax purposes. We always make sure that we have

a lawful basis for storing your PD. Your information may be retained in electronic form, paper form,

or a combination of both. When your PD is no longer needed and there is no lawful basis for

storing it, we will securely destroy, delete, or erase it.

5.2 Retention of NPD. We may retain your NPD for as long as necessary for the purposes

described in this privacy policy. This may include keeping NPA for the period that is necessary to

pursue our legitimate business interests , conduct audits, comply with (and demonstrate

compliance with) legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

5.3 Retention as required by law. Please note that, in some cases, we may be obliged

by law to store PD for a certain period of time (e.g ., we have to keep our accountancy records for

the time period prescribed by law). In such cases, we will store PD for the time period stipulated by

the applicable law and delete it as soon as the required retention period expires.

6\. Your Rights Regarding Your PD

6.1 Updating Your PD. You can update your PD using services found on our Website. If no

such services exist, you can contact us using the contact information found at the bottom of this

privacy policy and we will help you.

6.2 Revoking Your Consent for Using Your PD. You have the right to revoke your

consent for us to use your PD at any time, if you have provided such a consent. Your opt-out will

not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to

affiliates and business partners; (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers that provide

certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services and

data management services; (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests ;

(iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments, or as otherwise

required to be made under applicable law; (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties; or

(vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may

choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept. If you want to revoke your

consent for us to use your PD, please contact us using the contact information found at the

bottom of this privacy policy and we will help you. You can easily opt-out from our marketing

communication by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link included in every marketing email sent by us.

6.3 You rights. When using our Website and submitting PD to us, you may have certain

rights under the GDPR, the CCPA, and other applicable laws. Depending on the legal basis for

processing your PD, you may have some or all of the following rights:

• The right to be informed. You have the right to be informed about the PD we collect from

you, and how we process it.

• The right of access. You have the right to get confirmation that your PD is being

processed and have the ability to access your PD.

• The right to rectification. You have the right to have your PD corrected if it is inaccurate or

incomplete.

• The right to erasure (right to be forgotten). You have the right to request the removal or

deletion of your PD if there is no compelling reason for us to continue processing it.

• The right to data portability. You have the right to request and get your PD that you provided

to us and use it for your own purposes. We will provide your PD to you in a machine-readable

format (e.g., a .pdf file) within 30 days of your request.

• The right to restrict processing. You have a right to ‘block ’or restrict the processing of

your PD. When your PD is restricted, we are permitted to store your PD, but not to process it

further.

• The right to object. You have the right to object to us processing your PD for the

following reasons:

(i) If the processing was based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in the

public interest/exercise of official authority (including profiling);

(ii) Direct marketing (including profiling); and

(iii) Processing for purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics.

• Automated individual decision-making and profiling. You have the right not to be

subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces

legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affects you.

• Filing a complaint with authorities. You have the right to file a complaint with

supervisory authorities if your information has not been processed in compliance with the

applicable laws. If the supervisory authorities fail to address your complaint properly, you may

have the right to a judicial remedy.

6.4 How to exercise your rights? If you would like to exercise your rights, please contact

us by using the contact details at the end of this privacy policy and explain in detail your request.

You can contact us electronically (by email or via our contact form) or by post, whichever method

you prefer. In order verify the legitimacy of your request, we may ask you to provide us with an

identifying piece of information, so that we would be able to locate you in our system (we will

use such information for verification purposes only). We will answer your request within a

reasonable timeframe but no later than 30 days. We will provide your PD in a portable and readily

usable format. You can exercise your rights free of charge up to 2 times per year. We will direct

all our services providers, including Our Processors , to act according to your request. Please

note that, in certain cases (e.g ., if we need your PD for completing a transaction, carry out our

contractual obligations, comply with the applicable laws, or carry out our legitimate business

interests ), we may not be able to delete your PD from our systems.

6.5 How to launch a complaint? If you would like to launch a complaint about the way in

which we handle your personal data, we kindly ask you to contact us first and express your

concerns. After you contact us, we will investigate your complaint and provide you with our

response as soon as possible (no later than 30 days). If you are not satisfied with the

outcome of your complaint, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection

authority.

7\. Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties

If any postings you make on our Website contain information, including PD, about third parties, you

must make sure you have the permission to include that information in your posting. While we are

not legally liable for the actions of our users, we reserve the right to remove any postings about

which we are notified, if such postings violate the privacy rights of others.

8\. Do Not Track Settings

Some web browsers have settings that enable you to request that our Website not track your

movement within our Website. Our Website does not obey such settings when transmitted to and

detected by our Website. You can turn off tracking features and other security settings in your

browser by referring to your browser’s user manual.

9\. Links to Third-Party Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites. These third-party websites are not under our

control and are not subject to our privacy policy. Third-party websites will likely have their own

privacy notices. We have no responsibility for these third-party websites and we provide links to

these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use of and access to

these websites are solely at your risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy notices of any

third-party websites to see how they treat your PD.

10\. Protecting Children’s Privacy

Our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18. Thus, we do not knowingly

collect PD from children under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that

your child under the age of 18 is using our Website or submit any PD through it, please contact us.

Before we remove any PD from our systems, we may ask for proof of identification to prevent

malicious removal of account information. If we discover that a child under the age of 18 is

accessing our Website, we will delete his/her PD within a reasonable period of time.

11\. Our Email Policy

11.1 Marketing messages. Normally, we do not send you marketing messages. However, if

we decide to do so and you sign up to receive our newsletter or provide your consent, we will,

from time to time, send you marketing messages, such as newsletters, brochures, promotions and

advertisements , informing you about our new services or new features of the Website. We will not

sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third party without your permission.

11.2 Opting-out. If you receive any marketing-related emails, you will be able to easily

opt-out from receiving marketing messages by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link included in

every email.

11.3 Informational notices. From time to time, we may send you informational notices, such

as service-related, technical or administrative emails, information about the Website, your privacy

and security , and other important matters. Please note that we will send such notices on an

“if-needed” basis and they do not fall within the scope of direct marketing communication that

requires your prior consent.

12\. Our Security Policy

12.1 We have built our Website using industry-standard security measures and authentication

tools to protect the security of your PD. We and Our Processors also maintain technical and

physical safeguards to protect your PD.

12.2 We implement organisational and technical information security measures to protect your

PD from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, and disclosure. The security measures taken by us

include secured networks (we use SSL encryption), strong passwords, DDOS mitigation, limited

access to your PD by our staff, and anonymisation of PD (when possible).

12.3 When we collect your credit card information through our Website, we will encrypt it before

it travels over the Internet using industry-standard technology for conducting secure online

transactions. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee against the loss or misuse of your PD or secure

data transmission over the Internet because of its nature. We use third-party billing services and

have no control over these services. We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure

your credit card number is kept strictly confidential by using only third-party billing services that

use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorised

use.

12.4 We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and to not

share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Website when you finish using it,

especially if you are sharing or using a computer in a public place.

12.5 Security breaches. Although we put our best effort to protect your PD, given the

nature of communications and information processing technology and the Internet, we cannot be

liable for any unlawful destruction, loss, use, copying, modification, leakage, and falsification of

your PD caused by circumstances that are beyond our reasonable control. In case a PD breach

occurs , we will immediately take reasonable measures to mitigate the breach, as required by the

applicable law. Our liability for any security breach will be limited to the highest extent permitted by

the applicable law.

13\. Personalised (Targeted) Advertising

13.1 The Ads. On the Website, you can encounter personalised advertising and marketing

materials by video (collectively, the “Ads”) that are served to you as a part of our cooperation

with third-party vendors, including the advertising network Google AdSense

(https://www.google.com/adsense/start/) and automated advertising service provider Primis

(https://www.primis.tech) (collectively, the “Partners”). The Ads may be served to you directly on

the Website or through the video games that you play. We merely host the Ads; we do not create

the Ads or bear any responsibility for the content of the Ads. The Ads are

served on the basis of your visits to the Website and other sites on the Internet.

13.2 PD and NPD collected through the Ads. When you visit the Website, we collect your

cookie-related data in accordance with our cookie policy available at

https://www.throwawaymail.com/cookie-policy.pdf, as well as other online identifiers, PD and

NPD, such as:

• Your IP address;

• The domain name that serves you the Ads;

• The geographic location of your computer system;

• Your advertising ID;

• Your access to the Ads and your use of the Ads; and

• Information about redirection to other websites related to the Ads.

The PD and NPD collected through the Ads are used for advertising and marketing purposes,

such as:

• To tailor the Ads to you;

• To retarget content to you;

• To personalise your user experience on the Website; and

• To operate, provide, analyse, maintain, manage, and improve the Website and the services

provided by the Partners.

The lawful bases on which we rely when processing the data listed above are (i) your consent (if

applicable) and (ii) pursuing legitimate business interests (i.e., to grow our business).

13.3 Disclosure of PD and NPD collected through the Ads. The PD and NPD specified

in section 13.2 may be disclosed to the Partners for advertising purposes, in accordance with

section 3 of this privacy policy. The Partners act as data processors with regard to such data.

For more information on their privacy practices, please refer to

https://www.primis.tech/privacy-policy and https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en, respectively.

13.4 Consent. In certain cases (e.g.., if you are located in the EU), we may ask you to

provide consent to our use of cookies and other tracking technologies related to the Ads. For

more information on our cookie consent, please refer to our cookie policy available at

https://www.throwawaymail.com/cookie-policy.pdf.

13.6 Opting out from personalised advertising. You can control how personalised

advertising is shown to you or opt-out from targeted advertising by consulting the guide powered

by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) available at https://youradchoices.com. The DAA offers

tools for consumers to opt-out from using their PD for advertising (for websites and mobile

applications): https://youradchoices.com/control. For more information on opting-out from

advertising features on your device, please consult the Network Advertising Initiative:

https://www.networkadvertising.org .

13.7 When you use our website and enter your email address on our website (either to log in, or

sign up for a newsletter, or similar), we may share with solution providers and its group companies

information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed, pseudonymous form), IP

address, or information about your browser or operating system, with any of the following, acting

as “joint controllers” (as applicable and defined in the GDPR).

This Site is affiliated with Adapex INC for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and

Adapex INC will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. Learn more about Adapex’s

data usage here.

14\. Term and Changes to Our Privacy Policy

14.1 Term. This privacy policy enters into force on the effective date indicated at the top of the

privacy policy and remains valid until terminated or updated by us.

14.2 Changes. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to

do so, we will post those changes on our Website so that our users and customers a re always

aware of our data protection practices. For significant material changes o r, where required by the

applicable law, we may seek your consent. If you disagree with the changes to the privacy policy,

you should cease using the Website.

14.3 Repurposing of PD. If at any time we decide to disclose or use your PD in a method

different from that specified at the time it was collected, we will provide advance notice by email (if

we have it) and, if necessary seek your consent.

14.4 When you use our website, we share information that we collect from you, such as

your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating

system, with our partner/service provider, LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp returns an online

identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online and

cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable

interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt-out of this use, please click here (

https://liveramp.com/opt_out/).

15\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or would like to exercise your rights, please

contact us using the following contact details:

Company: Landocs Ventures LTD

Address: Hasaham 30, Petah tiqwa, 49517 Israel

Email address: https://www.throwawaymail.com/en/contact.html

© Copyright notice - This document is protected under the Israeli and foreign copyrights.

The copying, redistribution, use or publication by you without our consent is strictly

prohibited.
